[

](https://tepsa.eu/)

-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Search

Search 

Close this search box.

[

](https://tepsa.eu/)

Privacy Policy
==============

**What personal data we collect and why we collect it**

**Website**

We use cookies and other technologies to ensure website users have the best possible experience. When you visit [https://www.tepsa.eu/](https://www.tepsa.eu/), we collect certain data related to your device, such as your device’s IP address, referring website, country, what pages your device visited, and the time that your device visited our website. We collect this information purely for analytical purposes. This information is collected via Google Analytics. Google Analytics’ privacy policy can be consulted at [https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en-US](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en-US).

We do not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information about you. If you wish to restrict or block the cookies which are set by this platform you can do it through your browser settings.

When you register for our events, we may collect certain information such as your name, organisation, and email address. Whenever this is the case, we will explicitly ask for this information and you will have a choice not to provide it. We store this information indefinitely, but the information is used purely for organisational purposes internal to TEPSA, and is not shared with third parties nor used for marketing purposes.

Articles on this site may include links to or embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.) from other websites. Links to or embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website. TEPSA is not responsible for, and this this Privacy Policy does not apply to the privacy practices of such websites and the organisations behind them. These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

**Newsletter**

When you sign up for our newsletter, we collect information about your name, organisation and email address. We explicitly ask you to provide this information and explicitly seek your consent to receive email updates from TEPSA. You always have a choice not to provide some information, except for your email address.

We use Mailchimp as our marketing platform. Your information will be transferred to Mailchimp for processing purposes. [Learn more about Mailchimp’s privacy practices here.](https://mailchimp.com/legal/)

You can opt-out of receiving emails from us at any time, by using the unsubscribe link in the footer of any email you receive from us, or by contacting us at [communications@tepsa.eu](mailto:communications@tepsa.eu).

**Contact information**
-----------------------

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policies, please send us a detailed message to [communications@tepsa.eu](mailto:communications@tepsa.eu), and we will try to solve your concerns.

TEPSA Newsletter
----------------

The TEPSA newsletter keeps you up to date with the latest from our pan-European network. From editorials, analysis, and policy advice through to educational videos and event invitations, the TEPSA newsletter is the best way to get it all.

To receive the TEPSA newsletter direct to your inbox, subscribe today!

_TEPSA will use the information you provide on this form to share with you by email updates on TEPSA’s activities. Tick the box ‘I agree’ if you give your consent to receiving emails from TEPSA. Learn more about our newsletter privacy terms in our Privacy Policy._

 I agree

SUBSCRIBE

Copyright 2024 Trans European Policy Studies Association. All rights reserved.

About Us
--------

Analysis
--------

Policy Advice
-------------

Videos
------

Projects
--------
